palmbeachjewelry.com 2010-06-11

# Customer Service: Privacy Statement

Protecting Your Privacy is Very Important to Us 

At PalmBeach we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, and notify you of the following:  

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information that is collected from you through the website
  2. The organization collecting the information
  3. How the information is used
  4. With whom the information may be shared
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under PalmBeach control
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact PalmBeach by e-mailing [customerservice@palmbeachjewelry.com ](mailto:customerservice@palmbeachjewelry.com).

At PalmBeach, we are committed to protecting your privacy. PalmBeach does not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

The Information We Gather from You on our Website

We want to make sure that we provide you with as much information about our products and services as possible, while only asking you for the information we need to provide you with the services you've requested. Currently, we ask that you provide us with the following information: 

> **Catalog Requests**  
>  We would love to send you our catalog! In order to do so, we need your name and mailing address. We also ask for your daytime and evening phone numbers and e-mail address in case we need to contact you directly.
> 
> **Newsletter/Promotional E-mail**  
>  We need your e-mail address to keep you instantly aware of our special promotions and latest additions.
> 
> **Purchasing**  
>  We need your name, shipping and billing addresses, daytime phone number and e-mail address to expedite your order. If you select to pay by credit card, we need your credit card number, type of card and expiration date. We ask for your evening phone number as optional information in case we need to contact you directly. We also collect information about the products added to your cart and the orders you place.
> 
> **Tell A Friend**  
>  If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask the user for the friend's name and email address. PalmBeachjewelry.com will automatically send for a one-time email inviting him/her to visit the site. PalmBeachJewelry.com does not store this information, and it is only used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail.
> 
> **Registration**  
>  In order to use this website to its fullest potential, users may complete the registration form. During registration, users are required to give their contact information (such as name and e-mail address). This information is used to contact users about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for users to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.
> 
> **Surveys**  
>  We sometimes conduct online surveys which may ask visitors for contact information and demographic information. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve the site.

How We Use This Information

Ultimately, our goal is to provide you with a website that's virtually tailor-made to your interests. By keeping records of your purchasing history, we can shape the focus of our website and catalogs to personalize your shopping experience with us and make you instantly aware of products and services that best match your interests.  

Your Options Regarding Your Personal Information

If you do not wish to receive promotional e-mails, newsletters or promotional information from our company, here are your options: 

  1. You can e-mail our customer service department at [customerservice@palmbeachjewelry.com](mailto:customerservice@palmbeachjewelry.com).
  2. You may call our Customer Care Center Monday - Friday 8:00am to 11:00pm and Saturday - Sunday 9:00am to 11:00pm Eastern Time at 866-804-3745.
  3. All e-mail promotions sent to you will provide instructions on how to unsubscribe.

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, e-mail, or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our services, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by e-mailing our Customer Support service at [customerservice@palmbeachjewelry.com](mailto:customerservice@palmbeachjewelry.com)

How Secure is our Website?

We have taken every measure possible to ensure that your personal information remains secure. We incorporate the industry-standard SSL encryption for maximum protection. In addition, you will always be informed when you enter a secure area via a "pop-up" message. This message is our way of reassuring you that your credit card transaction is safe. Simply click to continue. When going from a secure area to a non-secure area, another message will appear to let you know that you are leaving the secure area of that site (if your browser preferences are set to allow this).  

All about "Cookies" and Log Files

"Cookies" are minute pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies contain absolutely no personal information about you. A cookie is merely a text file that allows us to maintain your shopping list between visits and provide you with access to your personal shopping account information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but in most cases you can change your browser to prevent them.

PalmBeachJewelry.com does not have control or access to the data collected through third party cookies.

Log Files: We use IP addresses to analyze trends, track user's movements and gather demographic information. No IP addresses are linked to any personally identifiable information.

Notification of Changes

Should we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes to our Home Page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what specific circumstances, if any, we may disclose it. If we should at any time make the determination to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from what is stated at the time it is collected, we will notify you via e-mail. You always have the choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. We will only use information gathered in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  

Legal Disclaimer

Though we make an effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith believe that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
